（上条(かみじょう)）
わたくしこと
上条当麻(とうま)は不幸な人間だ
I, Kamijou Touma, am a misfortunate person.
Looking at the past seven days of the Daihaseisai, this is obvious.
この大覇星(だいはせい)祭の７日間を
振り返ってみても それは分かる
Since everything's been resolved...
初日の とんでもない問題が
片づいた２日目以降にしたって…
I've accidentally walked in on Komoe-sensei changing,
うっかり 小萌(こもえ)先生の
着替えを目撃してしまったり
Fukiyose Seiri, after her unresonably fast recovery, headbutted me,
さっさと完全回復した吹寄制理(ふきよせ せいり)に
頭突きをされたり
Himegami Aisa whacked me in the head with a rubber ball,
車イスに乗っていた姫神秋沙(ひめがみ あいさ)に
ゴムボールをぶつけられたり
and, while being forced to partner with Misaka Mikoto during the folk dance,
御坂美琴(みさか みこと)に 強引に―
フォークダンスを
踊らされている最中に―
Shirai Kuroko drop-kicked me in the head.
白井黒子(しらい くろこ)に後頭部を
ドロップキックされたりと…
It was a pretty miserable time for me.
なんだか もう…
いろいろとボロボロだったのだ
繰り返すが 上条当麻は不幸な…
So, once again: I, Kamijou Touma, am a misfortunate—
（女子生徒）
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
大覇星祭 最終日恒例
来場者ナンバーズ
This is the Visitor Numbers lottery, a tradition for the final day of the Daihaseisai.
あなたの指定した数字が
見事に１等賞！
The number you have selected is the winner!
賞品は―
Your prize is...
北イタリア
５泊７日のペア旅行です
A seven-day-five-night trip to Northern Italy!
A trip to Italy?
イタリア旅行？
#14 City of Water
～♪
I know I'm repeating myself now...
（上条）
くどいようだが
上条当麻は不幸な人間だ
But I, Kamijou Touma, am a misfortunate person.
（上条）
あっ… パスポートがないじゃん！
I don't have a passport!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
はぁ？　パスポートって なに？
What's a passport?
フフッ… やっぱり そうだ
I knew it.
I knew this would happen.
初めから そう来ると思ったんだ
There are only two more days until our trip.
旅行まで あと２日
今更 パスポートを申請したって…
I can't apply for a passport and—
This is my passport!
（上条）
俺のパスポートじゃねえか！
I see. So I've traveled overseas before...
そうか…
俺は海外へ行ったことがあるのか
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
当麻 当麻 似たような物なら
私も持ってるんだよ
Hey, Touma! I have something like that, too!
Hey! You don't have any stamps or anything in it!
おい スタンプも書き込みも
どこにもねえじゃねえか
How on Earth did you get here?
お前 一体 どうやって
ここまで来たんだ？
So, Touma.
それで 当麻
結局 それがあれば―
Since I have one of those things, can I come with you?
私も当麻と一緒に
旅行に出かけても大丈夫なの？
あっ… あれ…
For some reason, I get the feeling it's okay...
今のところ大丈夫な気がする
俺は不幸な人間のはずなのに
But I'm supposed to be a misfortunate person...
We're not forgetting anything, are we?
（上条）
忘れ物とかって ねえよな？
Wallet, passports, airplane tickets,
お財布 パスポート
飛行機のチケット
必要書類に着替え
え～… ほかには…
required documents, change of clothes...
Anything else?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
当麻 当麻
Hey, Touma.
Why are you so anxious?
さっきから
何をそんな心配性になってるの？
Y-You're right.
そ… そうだよな
ああ 楽しんでもいいんだよな
Yeah! I should just try to enjoy myself, shouldn't I?
All right! It's our seven-day-five-night vacation to Northern Italy!
よ～し 北イタリア５泊７日の旅
For the first time in a long, long while, I get to feel fortunate!
久しぶりの久しぶりに
幸せ気分を満喫するぞ！
Yeah!
Let go of me!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）離して…
（上条）あ… あの… 何か？
Is something wrong?
（係員）これは何ですか？
（上条）えっ？
What are these?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
離せってんだから…
Crap! Hurry up, Index!
（上条）
くそ！　走るぞ インデックス
We need to get you some normal clothes before we can board the plane!
もっと まともな服じゃないと
飛行機に乗れねえってよ！
Really? You're going to buy me some clothes, Touma?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
えっ？　なに？ 当麻
お洋服 買ってくれるの？
1.5 kilometers to the shopping area.
（上条）
ショッピングエリアまで
あと1,5キロ
We have 28 minutes until the plane takes off.
飛行機の離陸まで あと28分
Damn it, such misfortune!
ちくしょう…
やっぱり 不幸だ～！
The ocean sure is close.
（上条）
しっかし また海が近いなぁ
It'd make more sense to say that the ocean actually surrounds us.
海が近いというより
囲まれてるっていうのが正しいかも
Chioggia is actually an island city surrounded by the Adriatic Sea.
ここ キオッジアの中心部は
アドリア海に浮かぶ島の町なんだよ
へえ…
（上条）
ハァ… 空港に着くなり 大量の
安全ピンを買いに走らされるわ―
The second we landed, I had to buy a ton of safety pins.
現地ガイドに
置いてけぼりを食らうわで―
Then, our guide ditched us.
一時は
どうなることかと思ったけど
It's been pretty rough so far, but at least we made it.
なんとか たどりついたな
In order to survive in today's world, you should at least be able to speak three languages.
今どきの国際社会で
生きていくには―
当麻も せめて
３か国語は話せたほうがいいかも
ウッ… こんな不思議シスターに
今どきとか せめてとか言われた
I can't believe this weirdo Sister is telling me that...
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
わあ…
We can eat after we drop our things off at the hotel.
食べるのは
ホテルに荷物を置いてからな
ク…
クギを刺さなくても分かってるかも
I know that already!
Food is nice and all, but we should at least check out Venice.
あのさ 食べ物も いいんだけど
チェックイン済ませたら―
No way, is that a real basilica?
ヴェネチア行こうぜ ヴェネチア
I've always wanted to ride in a gondola.
俺 いっぺん
ゴンドラに乗ってみたかったんだ
あっ… えっ？　あれ？
Huh?
Hey!
（上条）
お～い インデックス
Index!
（上条）
インデックス！
Hey, Index...
（上条）
お～い インデックス…
At this rate, I'll be the one who's lost...
このままだと 俺のほうが迷子に…
（女性）チャオ
（上条）ウッ…
Hi, is there a problem?
はい？
What?
You don't speak Italian?
（上条）
あっ… え～っと…
There's a Japanese person living near that restaurant over there.
え～っと…
ハ… ハロー
…じゃなくて 何だっけ？
Hello— Wait, that's not right...
Excuse me.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）スクージー？
（上条）あっ…
This man is my acquaintance.
Thank you for your kind help.
（女性）
フフッ… プレーゴ チャオ
All right. Bye, then!
My, should I have refrained from doing that?
あら ご迷惑でしたでしょうか？
You appeared to have been troubled.
私は あなたさまが
困っていらっしゃるように―
見えたのでございますが
O-Orsola?!
（上条）
オ… オルソラ！
Yes.
はい
Why are you here?
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
あなたさまは なぜ こんな所に？
（上条）
ああ　北イタリア５泊７日の旅を
ちょっと
I'm on a seven-day-five-night Northern Italy vacation.
What about you? Why are you here?
…ていうか
なんでオルソラは ここに？
Shouldn't you be in London?
確か ロンドンじゃ…
This is where I've resided until recently.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
つい先日まで こちらに
居を構えていたのでございますよ
その… ローマ正教から
イギリス清教へ移るときに―
There's been some trouble during my conversion from the Roman Catholic Church to the Church of England.
少々 バタバタしてしまいまして…
My bags are still here, but people from the Amakusa Church have been helping me move things.
まだ荷物が
こちらに残っているのですが―
天草(あまくさ)式の皆さまが―
お引っ越し屋さんのように
お手伝いしてくださるとかで
あっ…
天草式って あの天草式か？
The Amakusa Church? Those guys?
By the way, are you shopping?
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
ところで
あなたさまは お買い物ですか？
（上条）
えっ？　いや それが…
Well I actually came here with Index, but it looks like she ran off somewhere.
インデックスと２人で
ここまで来たのは いいんだけど
どっかに消えちまって…
It must have been fate to meet you here.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
ここで会ったのも
何かの縁でございます
And what perfect timing!
ちょうど良かったのでございますよ
Could I ask you to help me sort out my luggage?
荷物の整理を
手伝っていただけませんか？
Huh?
えっ？　あっ いや だから
俺はインデックスを捜さないと
Well, I kind of need to look for Index...
Oh, if you're looking for Index-san...
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
あら インデックスさんでしたら
Touma, Touma, Touma!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
当麻 当麻 当麻！
Touma, the gelato here is so delicious and cheap!
当麻 こっちのジェラートって
こんなに おいしいのに―
これでも
安売りのお徳用なんだって
あ～ん！
ウ～ン うま～い！
So good!
I found her not long ago staring through the window of a gelato shop,
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
先ほど ジェラート専門店の
ウインドーに―
張り付いておられるところを
お見かけしたので
so I asked a friend to bring her back here.
私の友人に お願いして―
先に自宅のほうへ
ご招待させていただきました
You abandoned me...
（上条）
お前 俺を置いてけぼりにして…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
あっ オルソラ お昼ご飯まだ？
Oh, yeah. When's lunch, Orsola?
Very soon.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
はい もうすぐでございますよ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
やったぁ！
Yay!
Such misfortune...
（上条）
不幸だ
He's the guy the acting Pope has his eye on...
（天草式Ａ）
あれが
教皇代理が一目置いていた御仁(ごじん)
Just how strong is he, though?
しかし 実力は いかほどのものか…
You're only asking that because you weren't involved in Orsola's rescue.
（天草式Ｂ）
そこに疑問を抱くのは―
あなたが オルソラさま救出に
参加していなかったから
He's the man who single-handedly attacked the Roman Catholic Church's stronghold of Sisters.
（天草式Ｃ）
かの御仁は ローマ正教の
戦闘シスター相手に―
武器も持たず たったひとりで
宣戦布告をした殿方なのですよ
They also say he saw the priestess naked and was sent flying with a single blow from her Shichiten Shitou.
（天草式Ｄ）
ほかにも
女教皇(プリエステス)の裸体を目撃して―
七天七刀(しちてんしちとう)の鞘(さや)で
強打されたらしいですが―
And he didn't even need a bandage afterwards.
バンソウコウすら必要なかったとか
He's a monster...
（天草式たち）
怪物…
（上条）
何だ？
その曲がりに曲がった評価は
What's with that messed up impression of me?
（上条･ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
うわぁ！　おいしそう！
Whoa, this looks great!
Is this okay?
（上条）
あっ でも いいのか？
俺たち 引っ越しの手伝いも
何も まだ やってないけど
We haven't helped you with your moving at all yet...
Accommodating you comes first.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
まずは あなた方をもてなすのが
先でございますよ
（上条）
じゃ 遠慮なく　あっ…
We'll gladly accept, then.
Would you like to use this?
（五和(いつわ)）
使います？
Thanks.
（上条）どうも
（五和）いえいえ
Not at all.
Itsuwa, how did the hot towel plan go?
（天草式Ｂ）
五和 おしぼり作戦の感触は
どうでしたか？
（天草式Ａ）
バカ！
結果を求めるのは まだ早い
Idiot! It's too early to see results!
The first step is making a good impression.
まずは外堀から埋めていくのだ
Isn't this too unnatural?
（天草式Ｃ）
これは少々 遠回りすぎ…
Aren't they eating with us?
（上条）
あいつらは一緒に食べないのか？
They're in the middle of training right now.
鍛錬中だとかで―
It seems they need to follow a strict diet and preparation methodology.
決まった食事作法でないと
いけないそうで…
Touma!!
当麻！
Go ahead, start before it gets cold.
さあさあ 冷めないうちに
どうぞでございますよ
Then...
それじゃ…
Itadakimasu!
（上条･ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
いっただきま～す！
うまっ！
Delicious!
（上条）
なに これ？
Woah! How can this taste so good?
パスタって
こんなに うまくなるもんなのか？
This is at least 500 times better than anything Touma cooks!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
なんか 当麻が―
いつも作ってる ご飯の
500倍くらい おいしいかも
You have no right to say that, but this is so good that I don't care!
（上条）
てめえに言われる筋合いは
ねえけど―
でも
ホントにうまいから もういいや
Delicious!
（上条）うまっ！
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）うま～い　うま～い！
By the way, is the main focus of your trip going to be Venice?
ところで 旅行の目的は やはり
ヴェネチアでございますか？
まあ そうなんだけど なんか
現地のガイドと連絡つかなくてさ
Well, that was the plan. But I couldn't get in touch with the tour guide.
I highly recommend you see Venice.
ヴェネチアは 是非
見ていっていただきたいのです
"The Water Capital," "Queen of the Adriatic Sea"...
“水の都”“アドリア海の女王”
Its beauty has given it many names.
さまざまな言葉で語られるほど
美しい町ですから
I guess we'll take a look then.
それじゃ ちょっと行ってみるか
インデックス
Index...
わたひは このほはんが はれば
ずっと ここに ひへもほほほ…
What the heck are you saying?
（上条）
何言ってんだ？
There we go.
（上条）
よいしょっと…
I guess I'll wrap up the plates next.
次は お皿の梱包(こんぽう)か
Orsola!
（上条）
オルソラ 新聞紙のストックって
どこにあったっけ？
Where did you say the pile of newspapers was?
It's over here!
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
こっちに あるのでございますよ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）フンフフン♪
（上条）あっ…
This voice and the sound of water must mean...
この声と水の音のワンセットは…
うわ～ 当麻！
Touma!
I'm all dirty now!
なんだか あちこち汚れてきたかも
Would you like to take a shower?
何なら
シャワーなど いかがでしょうか？
I'm sure you must be tired from the flight.
長旅の疲れもございましょうし
Whoops! So this bathroom is a trap...
危なっ… これは
お風呂場という名のトラップか
フゥ…
That sure was close—
危うく引っ掛かるところだ…
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
フンフフン♪
There's another voice in here!
（上条）
こっちからも声！
What's going on?
何だ これ？
一体 何が どうなってやがる？
What does this mean?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ･ｵﾙｿﾗ）
フンフフン フンフンフン♪
フンフフン フンフフン
フンフンフン♪
There obviously can't be two bathrooms.
大前提として
お風呂場は２つもない
One is the correct room, one isn't.
片方は当たり 片方は外れ
Damn, what's with this ultimate decision?
くそ… 何なんだ？
この究極の２択は
（上条）
右… いや 左
Right... no, left...
No, wait!
いや 待て　シャワーの音は左だけ
ならば 正解は…
It sounds like the shower is in the left room.
Meaning...
右！
It's the right!
I got this!
見切った！
At that moment, something occurred to me.
このとき 俺は不思議に思っていた
Why didn't I think of just knocking to check?
なぜ ノックをして
中を確認するという―
簡単なことが
思いつかなかったのかと
あっ… あら？
Oh?
Um...
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）あ… あの…
（上条）あっ…
うわ～！　こっちが風呂？
This one was the bathroom?!
ご… ごめん オルソラ！
S-Sorry, Orsola!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
な… なんか変なステッキから―
Hot air is coming out of some weird wand thing!
暑苦しい風がブオ～ッて…
（上条）
…て 右も風呂なら左も風呂？
Wait, both of them were bathrooms?!
この家には風呂が２つもあるのか！
There are two bathrooms in this place?!
Y-Yes...
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
は… はぁ… ひとつは生活用
One is for normal use, while the other is meant for use by the church...
もうひとつは 宗教用に
用意していたのでございますけど
今は引っ越しのために―
But since I'm moving, it's not being used for baptism right now.
洗礼場としての機能は
解除していますから
（上条）
理不尽だ！　反則だ そんなの！
This is unfair!
Against the rules!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）当麻
（上条）えっ？
Touma...
What are you doing here in the first place?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
そもそも
なんで当麻は ここにいるの？
そして なぜ人の裸を見ても
“ごめんなさい”が ないの？
And why aren't you apologizing after seeing us naked?
い…
いや だから インデックスさん
W-Well, you see, Index-san...
その… 新聞紙を…
The newspapers—
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ワーッ！
（上条）ウワ～ッ！
（上条）
不幸だ～！
Such misfortune!
My.
あら まあ…
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
では よろしくお願いいたしますね
I'll leave the rest to you, then.
お２人とも
お疲れさまでございました
And thanks to the both of you, as well.
長い間 引き止めてしまって
申し訳ありません
I'm sorry for taking up so much of your time.
オルソラは
これから どうするんだ？
What are you going to do now, Orsola?
俺たちと一緒に
どこか見て回るか？
Would you like to come sightseeing with us?
いえいえ そんな…
Oh, I couldn't...
I'm sure you two are planning on heading back to your hotel soon, so asking me to come along would be...
これから ホテルに向かう
お２人のあとを―
ついていけと
おっしゃるのでしょうか？
そんな… 大人数でだなんて…
...one too many people for that.
What?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
なに？　大人数？
"Too many," what?
聞かなくていい！　そして
知らなくていいんだ インデックス
Never mind! Don't worry about it, Index!
それに これからキオッジアに―
I was also thinking of walking around for a bit and saying farewell to Chioggia.
お別れを告げに
回りたいと思っていますし
長く住んでいた町ですから
I've lived here for a long time.
I'd rather not have you see me like that.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
それは あんまり―
あなたさまには
お見せしたくないのでございますよ
少々 みっともない顔を
するかもしれませんしね
I'm sure my emotions will get the better of me.
（上条）
そっか
I see...
Well, then. I'll be off.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
では 私は これで
機会がありましたら―
If you get the opportunity, I'd love to show you my place in London too.
ロンドンのお部屋にも
招待するのでございますよ
（上条）
ああ お前も
また日本に来ることがあったら
Sure. Same to you, if you end up in Japan again.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
その前に 当麻も
お部屋を掃除しなくちゃかも
You'll need to clean your room before that, Touma.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
まさか これって…
No way...
Is this...
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）みんな 伏せて！
（上条･ｵﾙｿﾗ）うん？
Get down everyone!
Shift mark right
ＡＡＴＲ
A-A-T-R.
（上条）オルソラ！
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）あら？
Orsola!
Oh?
Index noticed it.
（上条）
インデックスが騒ぐってことは
これは…
That means...
（上条）魔術か！
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）はい？
It's a magician!
Huh?
Where is he?
どこから？　誰が どうやって？
Who is he, and how?!
（上条）
ウワーッ！
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
当麻！
Touma!
ＩＳＩ ＣＢＩ
Turn thy blade upon thyself
I-S-I C-B-I.
あっ… 狙撃のほうは？
What about the sniper?
It's fine.
大丈夫　もう済ませたよ
It's over now.
（上条）
済ませたって何を？
What's over?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
遠くから
こっちを狙ってるってことは―
The fact that they were aiming at us from a distance means the person knows exactly what is happening here.
こちらの様子は
逐一 敵に伝わってるってこと
なら どこにいようが
私の強制詠唱(スペルインターセプト)を受け取るはずだよ
Meaning that, regardless of where the person is, my Spell Intercept will hit him.
Forget about the vanguard!
Bring out the escape boat now!
We'll kill the woman on the boat!
He must be the sniper!
（上条）
さっきの狙撃者か？
Wh-What?
な… 何だ？
（上条）
ウワッ！
くそ… バカげてる
Damn it. This is crazy!
こんな物(もん)が
運河から飛び出してくるなんて
How did they hide this under the canal?
オルソラ とにかく船に上がれ
Orsola, get in the boat for now.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
は… はい
Okay...
（上条）
これはガラス… いや 氷か？
This is glass...
No... ice, maybe?
Touma, are you okay?!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
当麻 大丈夫？　当麻ってば！
Hey, Touma!
How can such a huge ship sail in the canal?
（上条）
こんなでかい船が
なんで運河を進めるんだ？
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
陸から
離れていくようでございますね
It's seems like we're leaving land...
（上条）
ああ
一体 どこに向かうつもりなんだ？
Just where the hell is this ship headed?
Find them!
The should be somewhere on board!
What should we do?
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
どうしましょう？
私たちのことを
捜しているようでございます
It seems they're searching for us.
（上条）
分かってる
I know.
でも
飛び込んで逃げるのは ダメか
But it doesn't look like we'd survive that kind of fall.
Let's hide for now.
（上条）
とにかく 一度 隠れて
逃げるチャンスをうかがおう
We'll wait for a chance to escape.
Touma...
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
当麻…
くそ… 何が どうなってんだ？
Damn it. What the hell's going on?
行こう
Let's go.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
失礼いたします
Excuse us.
（上条）
ハァ…
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
どうして
こんな大それた物を使ってまで―
Why did they go out of their way to create such a huge ship to attack us with?
私を
襲ってきたのでございましょう？
（上条）
あいつら オルソラの修道服に
似た服を着てたけど
Those guys looked like they were wearing the same kind of clothes as you...
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
ええ　ローマ正教の手の者と
捉えるのが 妥当でございましょう
Yes, it seems they're from the Roman Catholic Church.
…てことは やっぱり
「法の書」がらみなのか
So I guess this must be about "The Book of the Law"...
あの一件は 私が
イギリス清教へ移ったことで―
That affair should have been settled after the Church of England took me in...
決着したはずでございますけれど
So this ship wasn't their main base, but only one of a larger fleet?
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
この船は敵の本拠地ではなく
その一部に―
すぎなかったということで
ございますか
キオッジアじゃ狭すぎて
展開できなかったのか
I guess the canal was too small for them to make a formation.
あっ… インデックスのヤツは
大丈夫なのか？
Is Index okay?
She should be able to use her cell...
（上条）
携帯は まだ使えるけど…
Crap. I guess it isn't turned on.
くそ…
やっぱり あいつ 電源入れてねえ
（上条）
…つか 海の上って電波届くのか？
Wait, do I even get a signal in the middle of the sea?
I wonder...
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
どうでございましょう？
（上条）
なっ… ドアが…
The door...
ヤバイ！
どこかに隠れろ オルソラ
Crap! Hide somewhere, Orsola!
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
でも
一体 どこにでございましょう？
But where could I do that?
Here!
ええい ここに！
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）アア…
とりあえず ドアを閉めて…
I'll just lock—
（上条）
アニェーゼ？
～♪
Agnese?
Next Episode
Agnese has a crazy plan in mind.
（上条）
アニェーゼを利用した
とんでもない計画？
A secret organization, "Queen of the Adriatic"...
秘密の旗艦
“アドリア海の女王”
Wait, Tatemiya? Even the Amakusa Church is involved?!
…て 建宮(たてみや)！　お前ら天草式まで
Next time: "The Queen's Fleet."
次回 「女王艦隊」
When science and magic cross paths, this epic will begin!
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる